const mondai = [
    { number: 1, question: '4727 + 5786 =', answer: '10513', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 2, question: '3627 + 6487 =', answer: '10114', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 3, question: '2549 + 8658 =', answer: '11207', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 4, question: '8579 + 2889 =', answer: '11468', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 5, question: '1859 + 8267 =', answer: '10126', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 6, question: '4678 + 5849 =', answer: '10527', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 7, question: '4648 + 5477 =', answer: '10125', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 8, question: '1827 + 9196 =', answer: '11023', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 9, question: '1568 + 9697 =', answer: '11265', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 10, question: '3979 + 6588 =', answer: '10567', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''}
];